shameless.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy - Shameless.com

This document details information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on Shameless.com

This site strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Web site.

DATA COLLECTED

Non-Registered users can use the search function, view videos, and access other parts of the Website .

Registration is required for uploading videos, and accessing a number of other features. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.

When you visit Shameelss.com, our servers may record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

When you use the Website, we may send cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies

We will never email you unless you emailed us first, or if we have serious questions regarding your uploads. We do not give, sell or make any use of our email database.

USES

We may use your information to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Website. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Website.

We use cookies, web beacons and other information to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Website and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views (including for use in monitoring visitors from affiliates). They may also be used to provide targeted advertising based on your country of origin and other personal information.

We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).

Your username (not your email address) may be displayed to other visitors of the Website.

We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third-parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms of Use.

If you upload any illegal material to the Website, or you are suspected of doing such, we may forward all available information to relevant authorities, including respective copyright owners, without any notice to you.

DATA SECURITY

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

YOUR RIGHTS

You are entitled to access and correct your Data. You can do it by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section.
